I just want her to answer one question.
Hey!
Today we've made a follow me to Abu Dhabi.
Please give us 40,000 subscribers.
I'm going to go to Abu Dhabi.
I found out I'm not going to do it.
This week we're going to go to Abu Dhabi.
We're going to answer our question for 40,000 subscribers.
I've asked Instagram to ask my friends.
Do I have any interest in my life?
I'm going to go to Etihad.
I first started Etihad.
I found out it was interesting to me.
I was working at Emirates.
I was working at the A-Lien-Coe company.
Then I was going to go to Abu Dhabi.
This time I went to Abu Dhabi and Abu Dhabi.
They were in the A-Lien-Coe.
I had to go to Emirates's website to purchase the ticket.
But Etihad had to go to Delhi,
He's been canceled at the end of the eight months
He's canceled at the eight to eight to eight to eight
He canceled at eight to eight to eight
ANDY HOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
I think the money is still worth.
4,50 years of退休 is very early.
Don't worry about it.
You can do everything you need to leave.
40 years of退休 is very small and very happy.
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it and doing the same thing.
Do small things.
Do good things.
So yes.
I think the money is still worth.
I think you're a great guy.
Why are you still not worried about it?
Derek.
I think you should be quite good.
You won't buy ADA?
What's the deal?
95% is Bitcoin.
And the shamanjaii.
I'm going to buy Bitcoin.
You can find a safe place.
I've experienced a new job.
I think if you have a job.
And this job is to keep you looking for.
And you can't keep looking for Bitcoin.
You can buy Bitcoin.
And it's fine to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to
And then you will spend more time to study it.
So the first and second is a difference between the two.
You will learn more about it.
You may love it.
You don't like it.
I'm curious about my favorite activities.
I'm curious about the different cultures.
I'm curious about different things.
But, I don't like it.
I don't like it.
But, hey, I enjoy my work.
I enjoy my job.
That's not good.
So, I'm just so upset.
I like doing this.
That's my interest.
It's myOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
But also, choosing to go to theOMOMOM
need to putOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
He can immediately need to leave theOM
He's also very powerful
So you have to have different accounts for each other.
Then you have to have a long time for each other.
For example, you have a long time for a long time.
You don't have to put in your account.
You should be able to take your account.
When you have a lot of information about your account,
what kind of tips are you going to do?
So when you have a lot of information about your account,
you should be able to ask him to ask him
And how do you do a lot of information about your account?
You should be able to do this.
You should be able to do a lot of research.
I always have to wear a lot of stuff.
You can wear a lot of stuff.
I don't know if I'm not sure if I'm eating a lot of stuff.
I'm not sure if I'm eating a lot of stuff.
But it's fine to make it look good toOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
because with theOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
It's also some projects to venture venture projects
and to encourage people to venture venture projects
to venture venture projects
Let's see
Bye bye!
I was always in the city of the city
and when I left the city
when I left the city
I always feel sad
because I have to leave the city
I'm still looking for a living
I'm still looking for
so I can't answer you
I'm telling you
the menu is very詳細
My God
I've seen this menu
It's a paper
It will tell you
the white wine is where
and the details of the past few years
and the stories
I've told you
My God
Thank you
Some companies don't have to wear a dress
I'll repeat it
I'll try to get it
I feel like this
The difference is
If I haven't
I don't know
So the entire store is very big
And from here
You can go to the back of the bar
You can go for a long time
The Etihad
It's a small
and cozy
and comfortable
I'm so happy
It's a small
To look at your career
What are you
going to be able to improve?
To look at the camera
Can you talk to the camera?
Because
Atro
I would go to the new place
And many places
So I would like to do vlog
Can you go to theOM
YouTube
I'm doing a job
Will you do a good job with women and gender?
Good question
I'm not sure
Do you need to do a job with women?
I believe many women need to help
This industry is more than a lot of men
And many very high-level discussions
If you look at the same age, all of the men are only two women
But you need to create something that only women can enter?
I'll call a question
People say, oh, you're a woman, so you're a woman
You're a woman, so you're a woman
It's a truth
But I won't always think about this
Oh, I'm a woman, I'm a woman
Who cares?
If you're a woman, you're no one will watch you
And if you're a man
You're a woman
Nobody's gonna watch you
No one's gonna watch you
The point is that you're a woman
The point is that you're not good
So, I'll go back to the question
Is this a woman's first group?
Maybe
Now, there's only a lot of money
There's only a lot of money
I'm from that time
To now
I'm just holding on
Like I'm the first one
I'm buying台積電
Now, I'm still still in
How to marry
You're interested in your fans,
just give good things,
and show your good work.
After all,
if you really like your fans,
you may buy your recommended things,
or use your favorite things.
This time,
your brand will be used.
If you don't have fans,
you might think
how to change my fans.
That's not the right direction.
It's a very different direction.
This is not what you think about.
You should think
how to make my own work.
Why not do you do a lot of money?
Because the market is high.
The market is high.
And the movement is low.
We are going to be more than
the price of the market.
Or the price of the market.
So when I'm not a rich person,
I'm going to build a lot of money.
If you start with a friend,
you're not going to talk about the topic.
You're going to build a relationship with your friends.
There are some good friends
who are helping you with your life.
who help you with your life.
Or he's a good friend.
But because of the times
you're different,
and you're looking for things
who are different,
who are different.
And you're looking for things
There are many people who are not interested in their family.
Like my friends, I don't understand their friends.
I don't understand their friends.
Don't let me leave a lie.
I want to cherish their memories.
I don't think that's a lie.
It's not that extreme.
Maybe one day, one day, you might have met a relationship.
And then at a different intersection.
There are some other issues.
Do you think the need to look at different directions?
I think the question is not the way to do it.
I don't know if I'm doing it.
I think I can do it.
But many people are trying to look at different directions.
I think the need to look at different directions.
I don't want to do it.
So, you know, you should be able to do it.
And you don't want to do it.
And you don't want to do things.
You don't want to do it.
And you think that's not good for me.
And then you should go to the next one.
Every single job, you should be able to do it.
I think that's the best way to do it.
You should be able to do it for two years.
This is a very bare minimum.
It's a very low level.
Because I think you can do it for two years.
You can get the best and the best.
You can learn some money.
You can't go to a job.
You can go to a job.
No, no, no.
It doesn't work like that.
If you have a job.
You've been to two years.
You don't want to do it.
You've got to find other things.
You're more interested in things.
I think you can go to a lot of things.
You can go to a lot of things.
But don't say that.
You can become a person.
You can't use it.
You can say that.
I'm going to go to a job.
I'm going to be a job.
But I believe that.
I don't have to be a job.
You can't be able to overcome some problems.
You can become a job.
So yes.
I've had to try to try to try.
But I'm going to try to try to try to try to try.
Hi.
I was told that you're the captain.
Oh yes.
I can see that.
The crew is great.
The crew is coming out and say hi.
But...
The crew is a part of the country.
And the place in the Olympics.
You can't shoot the camera.
You can't do this.
So...
You can't shoot the camera.
How about people who need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need to need
And then the travel world
It will be more
Because it is 40 or 50 years
And 60 or 70 years
It can be a very
!
But this is you can't experience
20 years old
If I am
I
I think that you want to be a little bit
You're not a little bit
But
I think that's a safe point
But I think that's the world
Because
I think that's the idea
And I think that's the idea
Maybe 60 or 70 years
It will not affect your life
It will affect your mind
But if you are 20 years old
You understand these things
It will help you a lot
Of course
You have to do it
You have to work hard to work
You know what I mean?
Yeah
It will need to go
Wow!
It's all in this little bit of a sudden,
and it's been a little bit of a sudden.
It's been a little bit of a sudden.
I'm a very strong person.
I need to崇拜 another one.
The reason is that
I'm a very curious person.
Because I'm a really curious person.
I'm going to find something new.
I want to find a reason.
I want to find a story.
You can ask a question and two people
to figure out.
This is not just a dream.
The next step is to buy a new year.
If you have a certain number of people,
if you have a certain number of people,
you can put it in the number of people.
You can put it in the number of people.
I'm going to find it.
Terry has a growth of the potential.
Really?
Jerry?
He's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's one who's
I don't have any other work.
I think that when a YouTuber
I do a lot of other work
is easy to do.
You can compare with the medical staff,
you can compare with the aircraft.
You can build a building.
You can do a job with the job.
It's too easy to do.
So I really don't feel like
everyone is so happy to do that.
You can do it.
You can spend more time with the energy.
But you still have to be very sensitive.
You can wear a building.
After doing different work,
I thank you for the work.
I really崇拜 the guest.
I invite him to come to our channel.
Isn't that just a dream job?
So I'm very happy.
And I thank you for the time and time.
For this time,
we have $40,000 to get to.
Thank you.
I'm not with you in it.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not with you in my car today.
I'm feeling it.
It's so awesome.
The cyclist today is 100 out of 100 people.
It's so awesome to see you at the end.